Guide to the Robert A. Caro Archive [DATE]–2021 MS 3203
New-York Historical Society
- Series XI. Scrapbooks, 1952-2021 (bulk, 1974-2020)
  - Scrapbook 13, 1988-1996 (Box [XI-10])
    [85b] Note from "Lizzie" on New Yorker wrapper dated January 15, 1990.
    [86] William Safire, "Words Out in the Cold," New York Times Magazine, undated.
    [87a] Princeton Alumni publication reporting on Caro, class of '57.
    [87b] "Book Notes," New York Times, November 25, 1992.
    [88] Anne Marie Kilday, "Barton got an early start developing political skills," Dallas Morning Post, April 3, 1993.
    [89] The Century Association, The Century Bulletin, November 1993. Notice of Caro's talke "Biography—More Than a Life," November 11.
    [90] "Horace Mann Salutes Two Alumni Authors," Horace Mann, Summer 1993.
    [91] Stephen Sherrill, "Don Byron. The clarinetist is a classical and jazz virtuoso. But he still can't shake his image as 'The Black Guy Who Does Klezmer'," New York Times Magazine, January 16, 1994.
    [92] Michael Wines, "Is The Press Being Too Hard On the Clintons—or on Itself?," New York Times, April 10, 1994.
    [93] "Eight Tell What They'd Do If They Had Coliseum Site," New York Times, July 24, 1994.
    [94-95] Satirical piece on the Library of Congress's plan to put collections online ["The Power Broker" would be retitled "The Bridges of Westchester County" to make it "sexier."
    [96a] "Biography Is on Schedule," unidentified, undated newspaper.
    [96b] Photograph of Caro next to two women at an event, undated.
    [97] "Knopf congratulates / Robert A. Caro / On the Twentieth Anniversary / of an American Classic / The / Power Broker / Robert Moses and the / Fall of New York / Published September 16, 1974."
    [98] Anne Thompson and Jeffrey Wells, "Hollywood's New Deals," New York Magazine?, March 17, 1995.
    [99] Theatre For a New Audience, "Henry VI Discussion," hosted by John R. Andrews, Robert A. Caro, and Robert MacNeil, March 4, 1995.
    [100a] Letter from Warren Wechsler, May 19, 1995.
    [100b] Letter from Jean Strouse, May 20, 1995.
    [100c] Note from David halberstam, May 21, 1995.
    [101] Ken Ringle, "Fiction's Truest Voice. Herman Wouk Lauded at Library of Congress," Washington Post, May 16, 1995.
    [102-104] Robert A. Caro, "Sanctum Sanctorum for Writers," New York Times, May 19, 1995.
    [105] Roger Rosenblatt, "The Triumph of Liberalism," New York Times Magazine, January 14, 1996.
    [106] "What Robert Moses taught us," editorial comment, Riverdale Press, December 14, 1995.
    [107] "Talking to Walt Harrington: Attending to detail, Striving for meaning," The IRE Journal, May-June 1996.
    [108] New York Public Library, Centennial Literary Lions program, May 20, 1996.
    [109] Andrew Carroll, "Banner: An Unprecedented Cross-Partisan Gathering of Political Leaders, Veterans, and Historians During One of the Most Divisive Times in 21st Century America." [No text; only images of Caro and Caro with David Rubenstein.]
    [110] Three photographs at a function; two show Caro with another man (resembling actor Gary Busey) at a table.
    [111] Wendy Smith, "Samuel G. Freedman: History in Three Dimensions," Publishers Weekly, September 9, 1996.
    [112] Katherine A. Powers, "The book as a gift is fraught with risk," Boston Globe, December 1, 1996.
    [113] Minutes of the Board of Directors, Fund for the City of New York, October 31, 1996.
    [114] Douglas Martin, "Aquarium Turns 100 With Renewed Popularity," New York Times, December 12, 1996.
    [inside back cover] Newsday Magazine special issue, "Reassessing Robert Moses. The Legacy of the Power Broker," December 4, 1988.
  - Scrapbook 14, 1989-1996 (Box [XI-11])
    Spine labeled "14." Contains reviews and publicity of The Years of Lyndon Johnson: Means of Ascent.
    [01-03] David Theis, "Life With Lyndon: LBJ biographer Robert Caro talks about his favorite subject," Houston Press, April 5, 1990.
    [04] Advertisement for "Means of Ascent," Chicago Tribune, April 8, 1990.
    [05a] Advertisement for "Means of Ascent" with note indicating it ran on April 8 [1990] in Boston Globe and Chicago Tribune.
    [05b] Advertisement for "Means of Ascent," New York Times, April 9, 1990.
    [05c] Photograph of Caro outside Bookstop in Austin, Texas; marquee reads "Caro's LBJ Means of Ascent Now Available."
    [06a] New York Times Book Review Best Sellers lists, April 8 and 15, 1990, showing "Means of Ascent" in 1st place (April 8) and 2nd place (April 15).
    [06b] Book-of-the-Month Club advertisement highlighting "Means of Ascent," New York Times, undated.
    [07] Laurence Chollet, "The Latest Chapter on LBJ: His raucous, ruthless ways created a Texas legend and revolutionized politics in America," The Record, April 13, 1990.
    [08] Deborah Baldwin, "Texas Mudslingers: Author Robert Caro traces the origins of negative campaigning in the electronic age," Common Cause Magazine, May/June 1990.
    [09a] Sidney Lumet, "Good, Evil and Lyndon Johnson," Letter to the editor, New York Times, undated.
    [09b] Postcard from "Diane & Clark," April 5, 1990.
    [09c] Typed note: "On March 31, 1983, some time after publication of volume one, Horace Busby wrote, in an op ed piece which appeared in the Los Angeles Times: 'Because Caro's portrait is severe and harsh, some of the late President's former assistants and associates have felt impelled to mount a counterattack against the author, raining on him abuse more appropriate for a political adversary..... The Lyndon Johnson appearing in Caro's prose is not a fiction. There was such a man'."
    [10a] Note from Dr. Gilbert C. Norton, Princeton '39, April 1 or 9, [1990?].
    [10b] Note from "Natalie" enclosing copy of Betty Liu Ebron article, "It might be Safer to get '60 Minutes' on Moyers case," Daily News, April 3, 1990.
    [11] Crown Books advertisement for "Means of Ascent," plus list of best sellers with "Means of Ascent" in first place, Book World, April 8, 1990.
    [12] Full-page advertisement for "Means of Ascent," Book World, April 1, 1990.
    [13] Martin Salditch, review of "Means of Ascent," Press-Enterprise, April 1, 1990.
    [14a] Robert L. Turner, "An excess of pride," Boston Globe, April 10, 1990.
    [14b] Publishers Weekly Hardcover Bestsellers, showing "Means of Ascent" in 1st place, nonfiction, April 13, 1990.
    [15a] Letter from Ted Ficklen, April 4, 1990.
    [15b] Letter from James K. Haynes, April 5, 1990.
    [15c] Letter from William J. Hudson Jr., April 7, 1990.
    [16a] Letter from Marth Weinman Lear, April 6, 1990.
    [16b] Letter from Mardie Lilla Petras to Ina Caro, April 6, 1990.
    [16c] Letter from Mary S. Miller to Ina Caro, April 7, 1990.
    [17a] Lisa Belkin, "For Quotable Expert on Political Messages, Phone Never Stops Ringing," New York Times, undated.
    [17b] "Hottest Hill Books: Caro on LBJ, Carl Albert on Himself," Roll Call, April 9, 1990.
    [17c] Robert L. Turner, "An excess of pride," Boston Globe, April 10, 1990.
    [17d] David Warsh, "Our own brand of Classic Coke was Eddie King," unidentified, undated newspaper.
    [17e] Letter from Alexandra Werner, April 10, [1990].
    [18] Fox Butterfield, "Is Life in New York City Really Getting Worse?," New York Times, March 10, 1989.
    [19a] Advertisement for "Means of Ascent," Austin American-Statesman, April 8, 1990.
    [19b] Best Sellers, Book World, April 15, 1990, showing "Means of Ascent" in 1st place, nonfiction/general.
    [19c] "People Watch" [Lady Bird Johnson on not reading things written about her husband], USA Today, April 11, 1990.
    [20a] Roger Bishop, "Robert Caro explores LBJ's ascent to power," Book Page, April [1990] (3 copies).
    [20b] Roger Bishop, "Robert Caro explores LBJ's ascent to power," Book Rack Book Page, April [1990].
    [21a] Dick Lyon, "Fancy-pants writer," letter to the editor, Austin American-Statesman, April 11, 1990.
    [21b] Max Lerner, "LBJ the moral monster and LBJ the noble achiever: Two men or one?," New York Post, April 14, 1990.
    [22] Perry Stewart, "Study of one life is taking another lifetime to finish," and Steve Neal, "The lows of LBJ," Fort Worth Star-Telegram, March 18, 1990 (multiple copies).
    [23] Letter from Avery Corman, undated.
    [24a] Sales Summary, Week Ending Saturday, April 7th, 1990.
    [24b] New York Times Book Review Best Sellers ("Means of Ascent" in 1st place, nonfiction), April 22, 1990.
    [24c] Best Sellers, Washington Post Book World ("Means of Ascent" in 2nd place, nonfiction/general), April 29, 1990.
    [24d] Hardcover Best Sellers, Newsday, April 15 and 29, 1990 ("Means of Ascent" in 1st place, nonfiction, both dates).
    [25] Alfred A. Knopf Incorporated, internal memo re: The Years of LBJ vols. I and II, March 27, 1990.
    [26a] Kendall Clark Baker, "Politics, power and corruption: Second volume of LBJ biography paints a sordid picture of his rise to the U.S. Senate," St. Petersburg Times, March 25, 1990.
    [26b] Christopher Lehmann-Haupt, "Johnson paid price for power. Biography details 'stolen' Senate race," Richmond Times-Dispatch, March 25, 1990.
    [27a] Joseph Sobran, "LBJ's Texas election coup," unidentified, undated newspaper.
    [27b] Dick Lyon, "Fancy-pants writer," letter to the editor, Austin American-Statesman, April 11, 1990.
    [28] Ralph Novak, "Means of Ascent by Robert A. Caro," People, April 16, 1990.
    [29] [blank].
    [30] Joe Mysak, "The Midland Machiavel," National Review, April 30, 1990.
    [31] Kevin Kelly, "LBJ: expedience is best teacher," In These Times, April 11-17, 1990.
    [32] Fred Bonavita, "LBJ bio stirs controversy," Express-News, San Antonio, Texas, April 15, 1990.
    [33] Fred Bonavita, "LBJ's life occupied biographer for 14 years," Sunday Express-News, San Antonio, Texas, April 1, 1990.
    [34a] Itinerary for "Means of Ascent" interviews and appearances beginning April 10, [1990].
    [34b] Letter from Paul Bogaards enclosing itinerary for "Means of Ascent" interviews and appearances, April 19, 1990. With.
    [35] Elizabeth Bennett, "The other side of LBJ—a Portrait in black and white," Houston Post, April 22, 1990.
    [36] "Of Men and Politics" [letters to the editor regarding "Means of Ascent"], Book World, Washington Post, April 22, 1990.
    [37a] "Even in death, LBJ looms larger than life to Texans," The Age, April 5, 1990.
    [37b] Letter from Luther E. Jones Jr. commenting on enclosed article by "Molly" on "Means of Ascent" [unclear if this is the unsigned piece in 37a].
    [37c] "Hardcover Best Sellers," showing "Means of Ascent in first place, nonfiction, Newsday, April 22, 1990.
    [38] Andy Grundberg, "The Personal Side of Johnson as President," New York Times, June 1, 1990.
    [39] "Lieterary Lights. Branch, Sheehan, Caro: Most thought-provoking authors," U.S. News & World Report, July 9, 1990.
    [40a] Peter Genovese, "Painstaking research for LBJ's biography," Home News, New Brunswick, New Jersey, October 9, 1990.
    [40b] Quality Paperback Book Club Review, Fall 1990, featuring "Means of Ascent" on cover.
    [41] Advertisement for Robert F. Keeler's "Newsday: A Candid History of the Respectable Tabloid," with endorsement by Caro, New York Times, September 22, 1990.
    [42] James D. Squires, "A Recurring Theme Reveals the Dark Side of a Future President," Nieman Reports, vol. 44, no. 2 (Summer 1990).
    [43] Richard Marius, "Having the Last Words," Harvard Magazine, July-August 1990.
    [44] Marjorie Marks-Frost, "1990 Lost Angeles Times Book Prize Nominees for the publishing year August 1, 1989 through July 31, 1990," listing "Means of Ascent," Los Angeles Times Book Review, September 2, 1990.
    [45] Gerald Kaufman, "Call me Landslide Lyndon," The Sunday Times, London, September 9, 1990.
    [46] Hugh Borgan, "Landslide Lyndon," [London Times?], September 1990.
    [47] Miles Donald, "Filthy Road to the White House," Literary Review, August 30, 1990.
    [48] Vivian [Bird?], "More tales of an unscrupulous president," Birmingham Post [U.K.], September 6, 1990.
    [49] Eva Hoffman, "Biography as Art Form Discussed by Writers. Methodology and Nuances Are Explored," New York Times, November 19, 1984.
    [50] Kurt Jacobsen, "On the way with LBJ," The Guardian, September 20, 1990.
    [51] Frank Johnson, "The first of the American dreadnoughts," Telegraph, undated.
    [52] J. Enoch Powell, "A presidential horror story," unidentified U.K. newspaper, undated.
    [53] Peter Genovese, "Painstaking research for LBJ's biography," Home News, New Brunswick, New Jersey, October 9, 1990 [three copies].
    [54] Clive Davis, "Real life, real literature?," unidentified, undated U.K. newspaper.
    [55] Article from Constitution: A Quarterly Journal of the Foundation for the U.S. Constitution, vol. 2, no. 2 (Spring-Summer, 1990) [photocopied pages stuck together].
    [56a] Postal card from M. Wilner, postmarked December 14, 1990.
    [56b] Photograph of Caro posed at plinth honoring "Robert Moses / Masterbuilder / Friend of Fordham.
    [57] Photograph of Caro shaking hands with another man.
    [58] Cover and table of contents, Princeton Alumni Weekly, October 10, 1990, listing Stephen Harrigan, "The Man Who Never Stops: Robert Caro '57 Redefines Political Biography." Article is not present.
    [59] Stephen Harrigan, "The Man Who Never Stops: In the latest volume of his best-selling biography, Robert A. Caro continues to reveal everything about the life of Lyndon Johnson. But who is Robert A. Caro?," Texas Monthly, undated [partial article].
    [60a] Letter from Ithaca College politics students, October 15, 1990.
    [60b] Letter from Hugh Gross, October 9, 1990.
    [60c] Letter from Tom Riordan, October 9, 1990.
    [60d] Letter from Frank Jossi, World Press Institute, Macalester College, to Ina Caro, September 24, 1990.
    [60e] Letter from Samuel Roy enclosing his recent column about "Means of Ascent" [not present], undated.
    [61] Katerine A. Powers, "The book as a gift is fraught with risk," Boston Globe, December 1, 1996.
    [62] David Remnick, "Johnson's Boswell: Robert A. Caro learns what it means to hitch one's life to another man's history," Texas Monthly, February 1988.
    [63] Certificate naming Robert A. Caro and honorary member of the Texas Ranger Hall of Fame and Museum, October 3, 1985.
    [64] Mention of Caro in Spy, October 1990.
    [65] Letter from Barbara Goldsmith, May 1, 1990.
    [66] Letter from Philip S. Turner, editor, Prentice Hall Press, November 28, 1990.
    [67] Photograph of Caro with Kitty Kukakis in Spy, February 1991.
    [69] "Best of Best," listing "Means of Ascent," Times, December 31, 1990.
    [70] Joseph Deitch, "Portrait, Robert A. Caro," Wilson Library Bulletin, November 1990.
    [71] "Newsday: A Candid History of the Respectable Tabloid An excerpt from the newly published book by Robert Keeler," IRE Journal, Fall 1990.
    [72] Quality Paperback Book Club material highlighting "Means of Ascent," 1991.
    [73] "Best & Worst," Entertainment Weekly, December 28, 1990.
    [74a] David W. Chen, "New York Bound Bookshop is Closing at End of Summer," New York Times, June 24, 1997.
    [74b] "Voice. Priorities for the Nation: Education and Housing," New York Times, January 21, 1997.
    [74c] Alfred A. Knopf, invitation to party celebrating publication of "Means of Ascent," March 19, [1990].
    [75] Mention of International Center of Photography exhibition "L.B.J.: The White House Years," New York Times, December 30, 1990, with a note from "Vicki."
    [76] Seth Kantor, "Want to liven up that dinner party? Just round up the 'Don't Invitems'," Austin American-Statesman, September 22, 1990.
    [77] "Taking His Measure: Five historians weigh Newt on the scales of times—and against other leaders," Time, December 25, 1995-January 1, 1996.
  - Scrapbook 15, 1997-1998 (Box [XI-12])
    Spine labeled "15" and "1997." Contains publicity on Power Broker in connection with 100th anniversary of consolidation of Greater New York City.
    [01] Robert A. Caro, "The City-Shaper," New Yorker, January 5, 1998.
    [03] Letter from Tina Brown, editor, New Yorker, December 4 1997.
    [04] Advertisement for Ina Caro's "The Road from the Past: Traveling Through History in France," unidentified, undated publication.
    [05] Library Notes, New York Society Library Newsletter, vol. 4, no. 4 (October 1997), advertising Caro's lecture for their author series, November 18, "Robert Moses and the Making of New York."
    [06] "Gilmore's Careful Climb Toward Top," Washington Post, October [15?], 1997. Mentions Jim Gilmore, Republican governor of Virginia (1998-2002), read "Means of Ascent" before launching his campaign.
    [07] Advertisement for "The Power Broker," New Yorker, January 19, 1998.
    [08] Jim Yardley, "Not Just a New Year: A 100th Birthday for a Unified City," New York Times, January 1, 1998.
    [09] Steve Weinberg, "The Changing Nature of Biography," Newsday, March 23, 1997.
    [10] "Radio Highlights," New York Times, undated, listing Caro's appearance on "New York and Company With Leonard Lopate."
    [11] Advertisement for "The Power Broker," on sale at Coliseum Books, New York Times, January 4, 1998.
    [12] "Celebrating the City and its Museum," advertisement for the Museum of the City of New York, unidentified, undated newspaper.
    [13] New York Public Library, Programs at the Center for the Humanities, Winter/Spring 1998, listing Caro's three lectures: "The Mark of Robert Moses" (February 18); "'Rabble? That's Me You're Talking About!': The Great Al Smith" (February 25); and "La Guardia vs. Moses: What Kind of City?" (March 4).
    [14] Advertisement for "The Power Broker," New York Times, January 25, 1998.
    [15] Advertisement for "The Power Broker," New York Observer, January 19, 1998.
    [16] Sam Roberts, "He Did It His Way or Else," New York Times, January 25, 1998.
    [17] Mention of Caro in Liz Smith's column, New York Post, January 25, 1998.
    [18] Michael Tomasky, "The Mayor and the Journalist," Newsday, January 25, 1998.
    [19] Advertisement for Caro's discussion and signing of "The Power Broker" at Barnes & Noble, Lincoln Triangle, on February 2, 1998. New York Times, January 26, 1998.
    [20a] "February at Barnes & Noble," listing Caro's appearance on the 2nd. New York Times, February 2, 1998.
    [20b] Invitation for "The Bronx: Reviewing 'Renewal,'" a conversation between Bronx Borough President Fernando Ferrer and Robert Caro, hosted by Leonard Lopate, at the Museum of the City of New York, January 22, 1998.
  - Scrapbook 16, 1989, 1997–2000 (Box [XI-12])
    Spine labeled "16" and cover embossed "1998." Contains Power Broker, LBJ, and miscellaneous topics.
    [loose inside front cover] Robert A. Caro, "The Johnson Years: A Congressman Goes to War," New Yorker, November 6, 1989.
    [loose inside front cover] Note from Howard Schneider, managing editor, Newsday, September 20, 2000.
    [02] Letter from Anthony Lewis on New York Times letterhead, January 6, 1998.
    [03] Memo from Patrick Navin, January 6, 1998.
    [04] Barnes & Noble Events, Advertisement for Caro's appearance at Lincoln Triangle location to discuss "The Power Broker," February 2, [1998].
    [05] Sam Howe Verhovek, "Hospitable Hill Country: A rolling landscape west of Austin is dotted with trees and wildflowers, but there's plenty of cowboy culture too," New York Times, February 15, 1998.
    [06a] Notecard from James H. Duffy, February [26?], [1998?].
    [06b] Photograph of Robert and Ina Caro at Jim Duffy's party, January 20, [1998?].
    [07] Ruth G. Davis, "The Power Book," New York Magazine, March 2, 1998.
    [08] Greg Barrett, "Noted biographer looks forward while dragged backward to LBJ—an JFK?," Gannett News Service printout, March 4, 1998.
    [09] Advertisement for "The Power Broker," [New York Observer?], January [?], 1998.
    [10a] Martin Arnold, "A Life Purpose for Biographies," New York Times, March 12, 1998.
    [10b] "Walter Scott's Personality Parade," May/June, 1998. Reader asked when the next [i.e., third] volume of Caro's LBJ biography would be published.
    [11] Invitation to birthday party for "Feiffer & Sorel" [cartoonists Jules Feiffer and Edward Sorel], February 19, [1998?].
    [12] George DeWan, "The Master Builder," Newsday, May 3, 1998.
    [13] Graydon Carter, "Captains and Kings," Editor's Letter, Vanity Fair, May 1998.
    [14a] Columbia University Oral History Research Office reception program, October 6, 1998.
    [14b] Cosmopolitan Club events for October 1998, announcing Caro's lecture on "The Power Broker," October 21.
    [15a] Photograph of novelist Patrick O'Brian.
    [15b] Photographs (2) of "The Power Broker" for sale outside a used bookstore.
    [16] "Die Metropole zum Guten und Schlechten geprägt" ["Shaped the metropolis for better and for worse"]. Printout of a German article on Robert Moses published July 21, 1998. With note from Caro to Roy [Ray?], presumably regarding a translation minus "the strictly biographical stuff about R.M."
    [17] Letter from Margaret Engel, director, Alicia Patterson Foundation, September 28, 1998.
    [18a] Dorian Friedman, "The draw of downtown. Big growth predicted for many U.S. cities," U.S. News & World Report, October 5, 1998. Includes quote from Caro: "Cities are the nexus of civilization... For too long, we didn't understand that the qualities that made a city wonderful were not huge public works but... the human values that come together there."
    [18b] Notecard from Dorian Friedman, U.S. News & World Report, September 29, 1998.
    [19] Photograph of Robert and Ina Caro, August 1998.
    [21] Tear sheet, Princeton Alumni Weekly, December 2, 1998, with news of Caro, class of '57.
    [22] Larry Hobbs, "Author discusses views of LBJ. Texan upbringing shaped Johnson, author tells group," Palm Beach Daily News, December 2, 1998.
    [23] Barnes & Noble advertisement for "The Power Broker," Time, December 7, 1998.
    [24] Richard Bernstein, "A Civil Rights Hero Inside the Law," New York Times, December 30, 1998.
    [25] Photograph of Caro and author Frank McCourt with an unidentified woman standing between them.
    [26] "60 Second Symposium," Times, July 13, 1998. Caro's response to the question of whether he would like to be the subject of a biography by another author.
    [27] Gerald Marzorati, "Heartbreak Hotel. The second volume of this biography of Elvis finds that his ultimate success proved his undoing," [New York Times?], January 3, 1999.
    [28] Letter from Barbara Gerstner, executive director, Dartmouth College Montgomery Endowment, January 21, 1999, thanking Caro for his involvement in the school's "Power and the Presidency" Montgomery Fellow lecture series. With printed program.
    [29a] Nicola Smith, "Historian Robert Caro. Johnson's Biographer Takes In Both Light And Dark Sides Of A Political Genius," Valley News, January 22, 1999.
    [29b] Menu, "Dinner in Honor of Robert and Ina Caro, The President's House" [Dartmouth College?], January 21, 1999.
    [30] Sarah Rubenstein, "Caro evaluates LBJ presidency. Second Montgomery Fellow calls Johnson brilliant, power-hungry," The Dartmouth, January 22, 1999.
    [31a] Letter from Debra Engelhardt, director, The Hampton Library, January 21, 1999.
    [31b] Letter from George Lang, March 10, 1999.
    [32] Update request for Caro's entry in Who's Who in America, 54th Edition (2000).
    [33] Certificate signed by Rudolph W. Giuliani, Mayor, designating Robert A. Caro a Centennial Historian of the City of New York, January 21, 1999.
    [34] Photographs of Caro with unidentified people.
    [35] Photograph of Caro (8 x 12 inches).
    [36] Printed photograph of Caro signing "The Power Broker" for college students.
    [37] Photograph of Caro (8 x 12 inches) with business card of William L. Perry, photo editor, Gannett News Service.